Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
Frieren.
The royal capital's in sight.
The adventurers are making
their triumphant return.
They must be celebrating in the city.
We'll have to look for work once we're back.
You're already thinking about that?
It's important, after all.
We've defeated the Demon King,
but it's not over.
We have the whole rest
of our lives ahead of us.
Work, huh?
I'd like something where
I can drink on the job.
Aren't you a priest?
I suppose you're right.
Frieren, the life ahead of you will surely
be much longer than we can imagine.
Perhaps.
Himmel the Hero,
Eisen the Warrior, Heiter the Priest,
and Frieren the Mage.
Thank you for defeating the Demon King.
Now our world will enter an age of peace.
The king's going to erect
statues of us in the plaza.
I'm not sure they'll be able to faithfully
recreate my handsome looks, though.
How self-serving of him.
He only gave us ten copper coins
when we left on our adventure.
Now, now, Frieren.
Tonight, we drink for free.
I'd say we're even, wouldn't you?
You corrupt priest.
It's over.
Yeah.
This is the end of our adventure.
It's been ten years, huh?
We've been through a lot.
The day we departed...
Himmel and Eisen were nearly executed
for speaking rudely to the king.
Kill them.
We'll give them a talking to.
Shall we lick your boots?
One misstep, and our adventure
would've ended there.
Sometimes, Heiter was too
hungover to do anything.
You're as pallid as an undead.
Are you all right?
No.
No, huh?
It was a weekly occurrence.
I, on the other hand, was exceptional.
We thought about leaving you behind
when that mimic tried to eat you.
Seriously? We told her it was a trap.
It's dark and scary in here!
Why don't we leave the elf behind?
We have nothing but terrible memories.
But I had fun.
I'm glad I got to adventure with all of you.
Likewise.
It was a mere ten-year adventure.
"A mere ten-year adventure"?
But that's an entire decade
we spent adventuring together.
Look at Heiter. He's turned into an old man.
That's rude.
He always looked like that.
It's nearly time.
The Era Meteor Shower, was it?
It happens once every fifty years.
Perfect for marking the
start of an era of peace.
They're beautiful.
The view's not so good
from inside the city, though.
I'm having a moment over here.
Don't spoil the mood.
Next time, then.
I know a place where you
can see them more clearly.
I'll take you there in fifty years.
What?
It's nothing.
You're right. Let's go see them together.
Well, I should go.
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to continue collecting spells.
I plan to travel around the central lands
for the next hundred years or so.
I'll stop by once in a while.
I can't understand what
being an elf must be like.
Seriously, how long has she been around?
To her, fifty or even a hundred years
might be a trifling thing.
Shadow dragon horns?
We don't have those here.
Haven't seen a shadow dragon
in twenty or thirty years.
I see. That's no good.
I need one for summoning.
Come to think of it, I think Himmel still has
the horn we got at the Demon King's castle.
It's exuding some kind of evil aura.
It's not harmful to people, is it?
I don't know.
You don't know, huh?
It's nearly time for the
Era Meteor Shower again.
I'll pick the horn up when I visit him.
The city's changed quite a bit
since I was last here.
It should be around here.
Frieren?
Himmel...
You're so old.
Do you have to put it so bluntly?
I'm still pretty handsome
at this age, though, aren't I?
It's been fifty years.
You look the same as you ever did.
I thought I'd never see you again.
The Era Meteor Shower, huh?
That brings back memories.
About that thing we looted from
the Demon King's castle...
You mean the shadow dragon horn?
I've never forgotten about it.
My cabinet's been exuding
an evil aura all this time.
Sorry, I think.
You could've stashed it
in a shed or something.
I couldn't do that.
You may not have thought much
of leaving it with me,
but to me, it was a treasure
entrusted to me by a dear friend.
I had to return it to you someday.
It's not that big a deal.
Himmel, are you ready yet?
You're bald, anyway. There's no point
in fussing over your appearance.
There are things we bald men
are particular about.
Now, shall we go see the Era Meteor Shower?
You've become rather dignified, Heiter.
I'm a bishop of the holy city, after all.
You haven't changed at all.
Don't pat my head.
Eisen, you haven't changed much.
Is that how I seem to you?
I would expect as much from a dwarf.
So, where's this place where we can
see the meteor shower clearly?
We're going there now?
It's a bit early to see the
Era Meteor Shower, isn't it?
Yeah. It's about a week's walk from here.
It's that far away?
Unbelievable.
You should be kinder to the elderly.
This brings back memories.
Traveling together like this makes me
feel like we've returned to those days.
We journeyed to all sorts of places.
Everything seemed so brilliant and new.
And you were always there
in those beautiful memories.
I'd been looking forward to the day
when we'd all be together again.
Thank you, Frieren.
Because of you, I had this delightful
adventure at the very end.
They're beautiful.
I think Himmel was happy.
You think so?
She was one of Mr. Himmel's companions?
I haven't seen her look sad once today.
How heartless.
Now, now! We're not wearing
sad expressions, either.
Show some respect, Bishop!
You're heartless!
You wound me.
It's not like I knew anything about him.
We only traveled together
for a mere ten years.
I knew human lives were short, but...
Why didn't I try to get to know him better?
Don't pat my head.
I should return to the holy city.
Let me get a good look at your faces.
This will probably be
the last time I see you.
Are you unwell?
My years of drinking have caught up to me.
It's divine punishment.
If you're ever in the holy city,
offer a drink at my grave.
Heiter, you're not afraid of dying?
We're the party of adventurers
that saved the world.
We'll surely be living the good life
in Heaven after death.
That's the whole reason
I fought alongside you.
You corrupt priest.
If you'll excuse me.
I should get going, too.
You're off to collect more spells?
There's that, too,
but I want to learn more about humans.
I see.
So I wanted to ask you something.
Seeing as how I'm a mage, having a powerful
warrior to defend me would be a huge help.
Give me a break.
I'm too old to swing an axe now.
Don't make that face, Frieren.
Surprisingly, life slows down
once you've lost your vigor.
I see.
I'll see you later, Eisen.
Yeah. See you later.
That's the tree I saw earlier.
I always get lost in these woods.
Where am I?
Are you looking for something?
Is something the matter?
I'm looking for the home
of a man named Heiter.
Then you're a visitor.
You're still alive, you corrupt priest?
Turns out it's harder than I thought
to make a stylish exit.
I brought some liquor to offer at your grave.
Would you like a drink?
I gave up drinking.
I see.
I doubt the Goddess will forgive you
even if you clean up your act now.
Thank you.
Who is she?
Her name is Fern.
She's a war orphan from the southern lands.
It's not like you to
volunteer to help people.
You're not Himmel, after all.
Frieren, why did you come to visit me?
I was in the holy city
picking up some things.
I've been trying to get to know the people
I meet on my travels as much as possible.
And I owe you a lot, so I came to
repay my debts before you died.
In that case, I have a request.
Will you take on an apprentice?
Fern has potential as a mage.
Will you take her with you on your travels?
I'm sorry, Heiter.
That's the one thing I can't do.
She'd only get in my way.
You know how often
apprentice mages die in battle.
I'm not sending a child my friend
asked me to look after to her death.
I see. Then I have another request.
This was unearthed from
the tomb of Ewig the Sage.
This grimoire is said to contain lost
spells of resurrection and immortality.
I find it hard to believe
such magic really exists.
That's part of why I'd like you to decipher it.
Can you do that?
It's written in code using pictures.
The people of this era
really liked this kind of thing.
I could do it, given five or six years.
I see.
But why do you want this deciphered?
I thought you weren't afraid of dying.
I have two reasons.
The first is that I when I said that,
I was just putting on a brave face for you.
The second is that I'm now more
afraid of dying than I was before.
Even if I can't achieve immortality,
I'd like a bit more time.
Besides, the holy texts tell us
to live healthy lives.
A long life is the ultimate
expression of that, Frieren.
You corrupt priest.
Also, in your spare time,
will you teach Fern magic?
As a priest, I don't have that knowledge.
I could do that.
There you are.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Do you always train in the woods?
Was finding me difficult even for you?
Mr. Heiter often tells me
I'm practically invisible.
It's a very good thing, isn't it?
It is.
It's true. I can barely detect her mana.
Her control over her mana is exceptional.
How much has she studied at such a young age?
Mr. Heiter said when I can blast a hole
in that rock, I'll be a proper mage.
Oh? Heiter knows what he's
talking about. That's—
As you just saw, my magic
dissipates and doesn't reach it.
I see.
What should I do to train?
Can I ask you something first?
Do you like magic?
Somewhat.
Just like me, then.
Is Fern's training coming along smoothly?
Are you trying to put on
a brave face again, Heiter?
It saddens me to see him treated like this.
But they're worth looking for.
Magic sure is amazing, isn't it?
You keep collecting the strangest spells.
It'd be a waste for you to die.
Someday, I'd like to show them to you.
It didn't have to be magic...